evening good evening and I'm from ukraine i'm andy
вечер добрый вечер и я из украины я энди
from belarus ask how you feel
из беларуси спрашивать как тут вы
about the war in ukraine and
относитесь к войне в украине и
well firstly but it is known that you
ну во первых но известно что вы это
ask this amazing i don't know everything seems to
спрашиваете удивительное не знаю вроде
be very clear
бы все очень понятно
but our country supports the russian
ну а наша страна поддерживает российскую
federation the
федерацию
country
страна
suffers and what's in  the general understanding is
страдает а что в общем понимании
correct, the leadership of the country, and so the
правильно руководство страны и так вот
leadership of my country has long been Europe,
руководство моей страны давно уже европе
the garbage of which I’m here to take,
то [__] которой тут находится взять я
in general, and
вообще а
you can learn in Belarusian in
вы по белорусски можете узнать по
Belarusian,
белорусски
come on, I’ll say Ukrainian,
давай давай я буду говорить украинская
you beat Ruska, we’re trying to
ты бил руська пытаемся чем мы заложим
spread it a little,
разметать я немножечко очень
let’s all close  without Russian, I’m
давайте все тесным без на русском меня
here to celebrate a small holiday, so I
тут небольшой праздник отмечать вот я
’ll most likely speak Belarusian very crookedly
скорее всего буду очень криво говорить
and
на белорусском и
I think that you understand Russian, I
я думаю что вы понимаете российский я
understand all the attitude to the Russian
понимаю все отношение к российскому
language and [ __ ] it, but just here, purely
языком и хер с ним но просто тут чисто
for understanding,
для понимания
I’m swinging the towers drunk there, switch
я башни качу по пьяни там переключаться
to  belarusian or ukrainian because
на белорусский или украинский потому что
it will be very crooked and oblique and
это будет очень криво косо и может быть
maybe understandable look  I, too, once revived white people,
и понятно смотри я тоже когда-то белом
for example, I understand Ukrainian
возрождая например украинские понимаю
calmly and understand Bernese,
спокойно и бернский понимаю
well, then I’ll try using Ukrainian
ну давай тогда я попробую по украинские
pornhub newspapers,
газеты pornhub
it turns out
это получается
like [ __ ] here, forgive
как [__] здесь простите [__]
me, I don’t have anything to say, it’s your people who
мне нечего сказать это у вас люди не
won’t accept guilt in Ukraine, it
примут вину в украине
’s very difficult to eat, I’ll try to
тут очень сложно есть попытаюсь
explain
объяснить
any problem  countries in that
проблема любой страны в том что в ней
people live in it,
живут люди
this is such a substance people are such a
это такая субстанция люди это такая
substance that smart people are
субстанция что умные люди их гораздо
always much less than
всегда меньше чем
100 people there, for example, there is a panel, for example, I
100 людей там панель например там не
don’t know they give birth 16 there
знаю рожают 16 там
I know such a married 20 these are such banal
знаю такой замуж 20 это такие банальные
examples, that is, but utter stupidity
примеры то есть но глупость несусветная
and a child to [ __ ]
и ребенка [__] воспитать и обеспечить
you can’t educate and provide from you, as it were, you are doing all this, this
не можете от вы уже как бы все это
is a minimal example with regards to the
делаете это минимальный пример касаемо
rest, but basically, without
остального но просто в основном ведь без
education, people who don’t need to
образование люди которым не нужно
achieve something in this life, people
чего-то достигать в этой жизни люди
who I myself also belong to them, I do
которые я себя тоже к ним отношусь я вот
n’t know, I’m sitting myself  I drink champagne because
не знаю сижу себе пью шампанское потому
it’s like a good reason for me, but
что мне как бы хороший повод но все
anyway, for hello, and
равно за привет а
I quit my job with
я с работы уволился с
such a counter job  l in a
таким противо я работал в отеле
Chinese hotel, five-star hotels in the center of Minsk,
китайском отели в центре минске
I won’t dissemble, I’m leaving Katya
не буду лукавить увольняться я туда катя
for a long time, but the final decision was
уже давно но окончательное решение было
made after the war, why, because
принято после войны почему потому что к
no one else is going to Belarus except Russians,
нам беларусь кроме русских уже больше
and
никто не едет а
many, as it were,
многие как бы до последнего дня до
worked until the last day before smiling
работал до улыбался
duty  from poison served this whole topic but I
долг от яда обслуживал всю эту тему но я
can’t anymore I can’t it’s not
больше не могу я не могу у меня не
just my fists that itch I don’t want to fight with him
просто кулаки чешутся я не хочу с ним
you are holy holy light from Vilna
драться ты свято свято светку из вильны
gentle to give or yes I am a person who, in
нежные дать или да я человек который
order to understand, firstly wrote a very
чтобы понимали во-первых написал очень
good review about my  organization
хороший отзыв о своей организации
completely consisting of all sorts of jokes counts
полностью состоящий всяких шуток графов
de
де
thanks such a questionnaire for decades
благодарит такую анкетку для декад
equals and secondly, today we don’t
равняется а во-вторых я сегодня мы не
know probably we need to feed and who to
знают наверное нужно кормить и кто
spread or that I came to work
выкладывать или что я на работу вот
today for dismissal completely in a
сегодня на увольнение пришел полностью в
white official suit exclusively
белом официальным костюме исключительно
in white I was the only thing  not
в белом меня был единственно что не
doing this purple tie and
делая это фиолетовый галстук и
with a can of Zhiguli
с банкой жигулёвского
this beer so
это пиво так
here I am so here
вот я вот так вот
I was exclusively white on  everyone
ну я был исключительно белые на меня все
looked at me like a [ __ ] passed us on the
смотрели как на дебила прошла нас на
street minus 2 3 a
улице минус 2 3 костюм
suit, that is, yes, there is a little bit of this
вот то есть да есть вот немножечко это
matter, the light
дело светку
is tetraborate and the places for these are
же тетраборат и места на вот такие
written off from the battle chosen for such
списалась из выбранной для таких
obvious battles, you, like us, the static action
очевидных битва ты как мы статика акция
on
на
agreed if I’m going to any situation,
договорили если собираюсь любой ситуации
ear  and to leave or go out, they went out,
ухо и уходить или выходить ходили выходе
painted the walls, the
красили стены
situation is [ __ ] [ __ ] me, most
ситуацию до хуёво [__] меня большая
of Ukraine, and not just in Ukraine,
часть украины причем не просто в украине
and
и
it’s on fire for me.  not only due to the fact
у меня горит . не только из за того что
that my relatives are so
там мои родственники так
good there, it’s just that I have
хорошо просто у меня
such people in the map why
такие вот в карте why
did my grandmother live as cousins as step-brothe
did бабушка живут двоюродный как
s, but still now, as my own children, I
неродные но все равно сейчас как родные
constantly call there and why and I c
дети постоянно постоянным звоню там и
n help, but in fact how far away ju
зачем и могу помочь но по факту чем
t call to tal
поможет далеком просто позвонить
with them, in fact, it’s very
поговорить с ними на самом деле очень
expensive for them personally, because,
дорогого стоит для них лично потому что
well, some attention, in fact, everyone
ну какое-то внимание одни по факту все
turned away from us, as it were, the family
отвернулись у нас как бы тоже семья
is also such an extensive one,
такая обширная
I’m half Russian, half Belarusian,
я наполовину русский наполовину белорусу
Ukraine, my relatives all
украине у меня родственники все
emigrated from Belarus there after the
эмигрировали из беларуси там после
elections
выборов
in 90-  x there, but when the Soviet
в 90-х там но когда распался советский
Union collapsed there, who was smart, that is, half of the
союз там кто был умный то есть половина
relative, here they
родственника вот они
are, the rest of Kherson, well, Kherson there, as
вот остальные херсоне ну херсон там как
it were, separate jokes if there is also
бы отдельный приколы если там тоже
a
где-то
grandmother aunt somewhere, but it turns out like a
бабушка тетя а получается как
rental of Belarus, the view is worn to the point
напрокат беларуси вид носится до того
that
что
Belarus has put Russians inside and  here the
внутри беларусь поставила россиян и вот
Russians from your territory will fire at
россиян из вашей территории обстреляют
us, I can only speak for myself, I am a
нас я могу говорить только за себя я это
dialogue starting what I say personal
диалог начав того что я говорю личные
puppey people are always no longer needed I will say this I’m how many of you can be here I’m not greedy sadly said with a fly 3 we see Russians and here you and Kozhin Kozhin say there is an American biolaboratory nationalist races a bunch of all nonsense propaganda Belarusians for about five minutes I really seem to hold 10 Kyiv people on jonin linearly saying wines which kind of wine is really this and it seems there I never eat a meal at the liturgy here with carved ones there for an intellectual I got scared with ordinary people nothing happens, I say we have the same people as in Russia, they are absolutely the same, it’s just that, in fact, if I still consider my friends there, I don’t know about it, taking some kind of social circle of people from us is much more civilized In general, I’ll justify myself for the day, I just initially blamed myself very much, well, although there’s nothing to blame myself on the other side, like in the twentieth year I got out
люди puppey всегда больше не нужны я
at least I don’t
пиздюлей разных я по крайней мере не
sit on everyone who got [ __ ] up or
сижу на все кто получали пиздили либо
my classmates have already left there
уже уехали там мои одногруппники
, we are students, we’re just me, after all, a former
студенты мы просто я все-таки бывший
student at that time, we were still
студент на тот момент мы тогда еще
studying, we
учились
left through Ukraine, more
уехали уезжали через украину больше там
somewhere far away through Karen’s, too
куда-нибудь подальше через у карен тоже
that is, we simply have no one
уезжали то есть у нас просто некому
to fight and the poor have left us in from the
бороться и нищим нас осталось в от
unclean and I don’t know what they are to do from this
нечистого и я не знаю что они из этой
evil spirits to fight this I personally
нечисти делать бороться с этим я лично
can’t
не могу
there I don’t know to collect some kind of circle of
там не знаю собирать какой-то круг
like-minded tributes I know our
единомышленников дани знаю наши
like-minded people whom I should keep
единомышленники которого мне держать
weapons will withstand weapons  [ __ ] on the
оружие выдержит оружия [__] на
territory of Ukraine,
территории украины
I’m like Russian battalions there, well, I
я типа русских батальонов там ну там не
don’t know there the last format, it was a
знаю там последний формате к это было
Russian battalion there, fighting for you in a
русский батальон там за вас воюет в
box, you know, vilifying the battalion to
ящике знаешь поносить батальона
touch Kalinovskaya’s knee,
коснуться колена калиновской
as if trying to stand there, it’s
как бы пытается стоять есть наши вроде
like ours, for our sake, we’re like slander,
как наши ради мы как наговоры
so I don’t know  I still changed
поэтому ну не знаю я все-таки изменил
my mind, I don’t think that Belarus
свое мнение я не считаю что белоруссия к
is an aggressor country, an
страна-агрессор
aggressor, I think that Belarus
агрессор я считаю что беларусь эта
buys this country
страна покупать
because I went to work yesterday and the
потому что я муза вчера шел на работу и
video is [ __ ] in the center of Minsk I live in the
видео [__] в центре минска я живу в
center of Minsk this garbage with the letter v
центре минска вот эту хуйню с буквой v
[ __ ] medical cargo of 200 [ __ ] was transported in
[__] медицинскую груз 200 [__] везли в
Minsk already damn it they say here in
минске уже [__] там говорят вот в
Gomel
гомеле там заполнены
these hospitals are full there everything else is not they are already in
эти больницы все остальное нет они уже в
in
минске [__] в минске уже сюда этих
Minsk, damn it, in Minsk they already bring these [ __ ] here, which
уебанов привозят не хватает который у
we don’t have enough clinics for Belarusians, and here they also
нас на белорусов клиник не хватает а тут
bring some [ __ ] meat, well, of
привозит еще и мясо [__] какое-то ну
course, of course,
что вы конечно конечно так и будет у
I’ll even have a video, I even have oil there and
меня даже видео есть я даже там нефть и
threw off everything else  that we already
скидывал все остальное что у нас уже в
have this garbage in the center of Minsk, well, what
центре минска эта [__] катается ну что
to do with it and I don’t know what the hell to do to
с этим делать и не знаю чертим делать
pour from here, but I can’t give coins
ливать отсюда но я не могу монетам
separately for reasons, it doesn’t matter grandfather, but the
отдельно причины неважно дедушка но
point is that, as it were,
смысл в том что как бы
believe more adequately than Belarus, there will
поверьте адекватнее беларуси есть они
always be, but unlike the Russians
всегда будут но в отличие от россиян
adequate, which are the maximum form of
адекватных которые максимальных виде
wrap or somewhere else, ours have already adequately
wrap или куда то еще наш уже адекватно
left for a long time
уже давно уехали
, but those who remained, I promised my grandfather the
вот а те кто остались я своему деду
first day when this [ __ ]
пообещал первый день когда это [__]
would end immediately,
закончится сразу же еду по
I won’t rest  as usual, because out of
не отдыхать как обычно потому что я из
my twenty-two years of life, 19 years
своих двадцати двух лет жизни 19 лет
every year, Ukraine, why, because
каждый год украина почему потому что
I’ll take a simple fig for the second time, but here we are my
простенький фиг сним во вторых но вот мы
favorite country, I have been to a lot where my
любимая страна я был много где у меня
father is a long-distance driver, he travels Russia, the
отец дальнобой он ездит россия
territory is still, by the way, there were
территория до сих пор кстати там были
some conflicts  with a Ukrainian he is
некоторые конфликты с украинцем у него
now in Europe, but it seems that during the day on
сейчас в европе но вроде днем на наши
our block or the truth will be forged there, but the
наши блоку или правда там выкует но
only problem is that they do
только проблема в том что они не
n’t understand, nevertheless, the essence of what
понимают тем не менее не 2 суть в чем с
we learn from them is very good cotton
учимся у них очень благ ваты будете
wool  [ __ ] [ __ ] clouds make deliveries
[__] [__] [__] облака вать поставки
this is great my father at least
это замечательно у меня отец хотя бы дом
wet the house with problems in another Ukrainians
смачивать проблем в другом украинцы
who moved to [ __ ] europe they
которые переехали [__] европ они
start giving it to truckers
начинают даем его ются до дальнобойщиков
on Belarusian Russian license plates my
на белорусских российских номерах моему
father was very unlucky he doesn’t even go
отцу очень сильно не повезло он даже не
to Belarusian he goes to
на белорусских едет он едет на
Russian because  that the company is
российский потому что фирма
registered in Russia and NATO, in
зарегистрирована в россии и нато по
fact, is not above them, and the meaning to
факту не находятся над ними и значение к
him in the clearing is to take a man 53
нему на полянке вот взять человека 53
years old damn well sk  oro will be the whole
года блин ну скоро будет вся
3rd one coming up in the parking lot long-range
3-ю подходит на стоянке дальнобое
young people in ukraine start
молодые в украин начинают до него
digging to his feet he says [ __ ]
докапываться до ног он говорит [__]
bug bug you
баге багу ты
why why why why they start
почему почему почему потому они начинают
digging you here on Russian
докапываться ты вот на российских
license plates drives supports he explains to
номерах ездит поддерживает он объясняет
look like in europe sit in your war
выглядеть в европе сидите у вас война
this is yours  territory why the hell don’t you go
это ваша территория чего [__] не идете
to fight for your territory of ukraine i don’t
воевать за свою территорию украины не
know what they answered to this you know what
знаю что они на это отвечали знаешь что
they answer to this and we have a swindler and a
они на это отвечает а у нас жулик и вор
thief we need to earn money to
к нам надо деньги зарабатывать чтобы
provide for my family
семью обеспечивать когда я обуваться
battles 200 brotherhood is people
в даль на боях 200 братство это люди
who always, regardless of
которые всегда вне зависимости от
nationality, always support each other
национальности всегда друг друга
here and the logic in them I am
поддерживайте тут и логика в их них я я
their petr yanulov this something much the
их петр янулов этому чему-то much the
city for here the euro lists of sanctions in
city for вот евро списков санкции на
russia was rus so olafur and still
россии был русь так олафур и все равно
let it pass on  the accounts of the
пропускают этому на счетах самого на
very souls of baht shares to cover
роблять души бат акции чтобы охватывать
not no shares our Belarusians do in
не не акции наши белорусы делают в этом
all this all this is the whole joke on all Belarusians
всем этом весь прикол на все белорусы
cat  some moved to poland doing actions
которые переехали в польшу делают акции
at the border and there are now huge [ __ ]
на границе и там сейчас огромные [__]
traffic jams are huge in a kilometer at the bottom of the
пробки огромны в километр низу
trucks it's another thing when you are
грузовиков это одно другое дело когда ты
specifically scared to the point of a person and
конкретно дает боишься до человека а
then well, how did the story end my father
потом ну как закончился историю мой отец
he just said it otherwise they didn't
он просто это сказал иначе не сделали
miss the head went into themselves
пропустивший голову ушли в себя по
at the same time, my father’s colleague was
при этом коллега моего отца
also standing in a slightly different place
тоже стоял немножечко в другом месте
when he was also dug up by Ukrainian
когда него тоже докопались украинцы
truckers, but they started we immediately
дальнобойщики но они начали мы сразу же
hack the car he was one of them, he
херачить машину он одного из них он
would throw off a 30 kilogram 35 kilogram weight to one of them because he was a jock he
килограммовую гирю потому что он качок у
had at hand  he walled his body on
него под рукой было он стену телу на
his head from the window, I don’t know how it is for a
голову из окна я не знаю как это
person to [ __ ]
человеку [__]
run away right away and I don’t support
убежали сразу и я не поддерживаю
what you need to fight there somehow, you’re
то что нужно там как-то сражаться там вы
[ __ ] on the wrong fronts, that is, this is
[__] не на тех фронтах то есть это
my personal topic, my personal topic, because
лично моя тема лично моя тема потому что
well, I have hats  there is a father
ну шапки у меня там отец
quality frontal exchanges he is not a young
качество лобовые размены он не молодой
man I support him as much as possible if
человек я его максимально поддержку будь
I am there I have full respect for the borders
я там я имею полное уважение к границам
I understand their hatred for Russia e  then I also
понимаю их ненависть к россии это я тоже
hate Russia like most
ненавижу россии как и большинство
adequate people are also complete [ __ ] up but
адекватных людей тоже полный [__] но
[ __ ] and fight to my father were I
[__] да и бьетесь до моего отца были я
will [ __ ] the language in the same way well let’s
буду нахуй язык точно так же ну давай
immediately get the thing out then let’s say
сразу вещь получается тогда штука скажем
you’ll be a trucker Russian
будете дальнобойщик российский
Belarusian so wines about the prices for the pit
белорусский так вин про цены на пит
market of Russia belarus  but it
рынку россии беларусь а
just turns out that people are inci Ukrainians,
просто получается и люди inci украинцы
so I’m their melody by people and I’m not their
вот я их мелодику людьми и я их не
logic petr to him this is their task, since
логику петр ему этому ихняя задача благо
you’re completely at
ты полностью
home and there’s no mistake, then the next
домах и дела нет ошибкой то следующим
filling, I’m not talking about something that doesn’t
насыпка я же говорим не про то что не
block that he doesn’t
блокирует что он не
think, yes, but
задумываются да но
they just  let’s give a lutsa we arrived, we can
они просто даем луца доехала мы можем
they wanted to block the
они хотели заблокировать
movement they would do like all
перемещение они бы делали как все
other people and on the border with Poland
остальные люди и на границе с польшей
there
там
this is what I call blocking and here
вот это вот я называю блокирование а тут
it is to give the experience of specific people my father
это дать опыт конкретных людей мой отец
less let Russia not find people here but
менее давай россии не тут найду людей а
before people in specific cars
до людей на конкретных машинах
so that my father’s
чтобы мой отец
experience of the team only turns out you know
опытом команда только получается знаешь
it’s worth the
стоит
ship comes out with a smaller ensign all
корабль выходит меньшим прапором все
propellers like suttle from the regions of ukraine and
винты типа сутиль из областей украины и
yes not  come to his senses, so
да не одумается поэтому
I just don’t say that in the summer
я просто я же не говорю что летом как то
somehow erase the Ukrainians about this, I
за стирай украинцы по этому поводу я
perfectly understand the reasons, I perfectly
прекрасно понимаю причины я прекрасно
understand, I just know
понимаю я просто знаю
[music]
[музыка]
because I managed to answer
потому что я сумел ответить
just to [ __ ] him off because
чтобы от него просто отъебать потому что
at least I have a son, of course not  over
как минимум есть я сын конечно не сверх
perfect and not superhuman, but still
идеальный и не сверхчеловек но все-таки
I speak from their diesels for freedom, I beat, I
я говорю с их дизелей за свободу я бью я
didn’t get freedom, and according to all this,
свободы не получил и по словам все это
ours somewhat continued to send
наше несколько продолжала нахер слать
this Russian
эту русскую там
movement there, I don’t say that I’m switching to the
движуху я не говорю что это перехожу на
Belarusian language, I still think  in
белорусский язык я все-таки думаю на
Russian, I speak, I mostly
русском я говорю я по большей части
Russian, I mean something else, I mean the
русские имею ввиду другое имею виду
relationship to specific people
отношения конкретным людям
here I’m a bazaar a little filter of cutlets to
тут я базар немножечко фильтру котлет
name Ukraine I support of course
назвать украина поддерживаю конечно же
it’s [ __ ] up when it kills in their relatives and
это [__] когда убивает в их родных и
loved ones, it’s about me, nothing
любимых близких это обо мне ничего на
to say about it, they probably already spoke about it
это сказать об этом высказались уже
many people in the media space,
наверное много кто в медиа-пространстве
at least from well-known people,
как минимум из известных людей
someone spoke out for someone spoke out
кто-то высказался за кто-то высказался
against earth rest in peace to those who spoke in favor of
против земля пухом тем кто высказался за
hope  I don’t know that
надеюсь что
they need to be eaten by some [ __ ] people and I
их нужно сожрут [__] какие-нибудь и не
don’t know, but I’ll do it because
знаю но станет с ними сделаю потому что
it’s [ __ ] [ __ ] up these 90 points 71
это [__] [__] эти 90 пунктов 71
percent of Russia says it supports this
процент россия говорит поддерживает эту
garbage, but he very accurately also speaking about
хуйню но он очень точно также говоря про
93 we had no [ __ ] n93
93 у нас было ни хуя n93
okay on the Internet is good  I will continue
окей в интернете хорошо буду дальше
to run, thank you for the conversation, we
бежать спасибо тебе за разговор
celebrated the flower, I heat the Kurinskaya
отпраздновали цветку отапливаю куринская
scroll, of course, you are handsome, everything is fine, and the
свитка ты конечно красавчик хорошо все и
words Belarus in Belarus, the morning shower is
слова беларусь в беларусь утренний душ
all
все